leafly.com 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy - Leafly

Last updated: March 22, 2018

Welcome to Leafly.com (the “Site”) Leafly.ca, Leafly.de and related sub-domains, mobile and/or software applications, provided by Leafly Holdings, Inc., and its affiliates, subsidiaries, parent company and other related companies (“Us”, “We”, or Leafly). This Leafly Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes the information we gather from you when you use the Site, mobile applications, and related services (together, the “Services”) and how we use, process, and disclose that information. We may add to this Policy with other notices. We may also post additional privacy statements for some portions of the Services. By submitting personal information through our Services, you expressly consent to the transfer of your personal data to our servers in the U.S. for our collection, use, and disclosure in accordance with this Policy.

Data Controller

Leafly provides services to users throughout the world. If you live in Canada, Leafly Canada, Ltd.C is the data controller for your information. If you live in Europe, Leafly Holdings GmbH is the data controller. If you live outside of the EU and Canada, Leafly Holdings, Inc. is the data controller.

International Privacy Laws

If you are visiting the Services from outside the United States, please be aware that you are sending information to the United States where our servers are located. That information may then be transferred within the United States or back out of the United States to other countries outside of your country of residence, depending on the type of information and how it is stored by us. These countries (including the United States) may not necessarily have the data protection laws as comprehensive or protective as those in your country of residence; however, our collection, storage, and use of your information will at all times be governed by this Privacy Policy.

Information We Collect from You Through Your Use of the Site

Our Service: When you use our service, you affirmatively consent to the Terms of Service and Privacy Policy. You may provide us with additional information by filling in forms on the Site or by corresponding with us by phone, text, email, live chat, or otherwise. When you create an account Service, we collect the following types of information from you:

  * Name;
  * Contact information such as your email address and phone number;
  * Demographics information such as your gender and location;
  * Any other information that you provide us, such as reviews, content, and bio.

We automatically collect information about how you use our services, for example, pages you have viewed. We also collect certain technical information about your device including your Internet protocol address, geo-location information, your browser type, language and identifying information, your operating system and application version, device types, device model and manufacturer, device identifiers, and your device operating system type and version. 

Cookies and Tracking Technologies : We also use cookies, Web beacons, and URL information to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the information for which you searched and which you viewed. Cookies are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing a website. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent cookies (which usually stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our Site. We also use cookies for data analytics purposes, including from Google Analytics. You can find more information on how Google uses data from these cookies at  [google.com/policies/privacy/partners](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners). You should consult your web browser to modify your cookie settings. Please note that if you delete or choose not to accept cookies from us, you may be missing out on certain features of our Platform. Web beacons are digital images that are used to log information on the Services or in our emails. We use Web beacons to manage cookies, count visits, and to learn what marketing works and what does not. We also use Web beacons to tell if you open or act on our emails.

Others, including third-party analytics service providers and advertising partners, may also collect personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different Web sites when you use our Services, including as described in this Privacy Policy. This Policy does not apply to and we are not responsible for those other parties. Third-party analytics services may use cookies and web beacons through our Site (for example Google Analytics and ChartBeat) and platform device identifiers and software agents on and through our mobile Services (for example Swrve) to provide us with information about how you use and interact with our Site. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of these third parties to learn about your choices about information they collect from you.

Social Network Services: If you create an account using, or otherwise connect your account to, a social networking services account (e.g. Twitter or Facebook), we may also collect information provided to us by such social networking service including for example your: name; email address; birthday; geographic location; interests; profile picture; gender; networks; user ID; list of friends; and any information you have made public on such social networking account.

Your Sharing of Your Information

The Leafly Services may allow you to connect and share your actions, comments, content, profile, and information publicly or with other people. You may control some of the categories of personal information shared via your profile from the account settings menu on the Site. Please be mindful of your own privacy needs as you choose who to connect with and what to share and make public. We cannot control the privacy or security of information you choose to make public or share with others.

The Services may also provide you with the option to share certain information from your Leafly account with social networking services like Facebook, Google, or Twitter. We are not responsible for the use or re-sharing by others of any of your information once it is made public. If you do not want your information to be made public, you should not use the Leafly Services in this manner and/or you should adjust your privacy settings on the applicable social networking service accordingly. We are not responsible for and we do not control these social networking services privacy practices. Please review the applicable privacy policy for information about how they use your information.

How Leafly Uses Your Information

Leafly generally uses your information to:

  * Facilitate the creation of and secure your account on the Services;
  * Identify you as a user in our system;
  * Provide, personalize, and improve the Services;
  * Communicate with you about your use of the Services;
  * Develop new products and services,
  * Customize the advertising you view and recommend content;
  * Fulfill your requests;
  * Send newsletters, surveys, offers, and promotional materials related to the Services and for other marketing purposes of Leafly using your contact information;
  * Protect, investigate, and prevent potentially fraudulent, unauthorized, or illegal activities;
  * Protect our rights and the rights of other users; and
  * As otherwise described in this Privacy Policy or in notices we provided to you.

We may also use your information to verify your geographic location. We may use your geographic location data to personalize our Service, to recommend content, determine whether the information you have requested is available in your location. If Information is aggregated or de-identified so it is no longer reasonably associated with an identified or identifiable natural person, Leafly may use it for any business purpose.

How Leafly Discloses Your Information

We may share your information as follows:

  * We may share your personal information with your consent or at your direction.
  * We may also share your personal information with others who perform services on our behalf (for example, with Twilio if you make a call or receive/respond to a text using the Service).
  * We may share your information with third-party service providers to fulfill your requests, including product reservation requests.
  * We may disclose your information if we believe we are required to do so by law, or to comply with a court order, judicial or other government subpoena, or warrant.
  * We also may disclose your information if we believe doing so is appropriate or necessary to prevent any liability, or fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses or to protect Leafly and our Services; or any rights, property, or personal safety of Leafly or others.
  * In the event that Leafly is or may be acquired by or merged with another company or involved in any other business deal (or negotiation of a business deal) involving sale or transfer of all or part of our business or assets, we may transfer or assign your information as part of or in connection with the transaction. Finally, in the event of insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership, information may be transferred as a business asset.

We may also share aggregated and anonymized data with our partners, advertisers, and other third parties.

Third-Party Advertisers and Links

We permit advertisements to be delivered to you by third-party Internet advertising companies (also called ad networks or network advertisers). These companies may use cookies, Web beacons, platform device identifiers, software agents, and other technologies to collect non-personally identifiable information about your visits over time on our Service and across other websites to deliver advertisements to you targeted to your interests, measure their effectiveness and personalize advertising content, and to understand the usage and visitation of the Services and the other applications and websites tracked by these advertising companies. We do not have access to or control over cookies, Web beacons, platform device identifiers, software agents, or other technologies that they may use. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of third party advertisers. You should check the privacy policy of the third-party advertiser to determine how it handles information it separately collects from you. In addition, the  [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) offers information about some of the Internet advertising companies we may use.

Data Security and Transfer

Leafly is built on the Amazon Web Services (AWS) platform and utilizes AWS for its data storage and transfer services. Details on AWS security certifications and procedures may be found  [here](https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/Security/AWS_Security_Whitepaper.pdf). In addition to the security tools on AWS, Leafly takes commercially reasonable steps to help protect your Information against loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, or disclosure. No company can fully prevent security risks, however. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. To help protect yourself and your information, choose a unique password for our Services and do not use a password on our Services that you would use on any other website or online service.

To the extent that Leafly’s processing of your personal information is subject to the General Data Protection Regulation, Leafly relies on your consent, given through affirmative assent upon visiting the Leafly Site, to process your information data. Leafly may also process information that constitutes your personal information for direct marketing purposes and you have a right to object to Leafly’s use of your personal information for this purpose at any time.

Information Choices

You may opt out of receiving marketing/promotional emails from Leafly by following the instructions in those emails or by reviewing the settings in your account. You may opt out of receiving marketing/promotional text messages from Leafly at any time by replying STOP to a marketing/promotional text message. You may opt out of marketing/promotional emails by updating your settings in your Leafly account. If you opt out of receiving marketing/promotional emails and/or text messages, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about your accounts or our ongoing business relations. You may also send requests about your personal information, including changes to your contact preferences, changes to or deletions of your information or content you post, and requests to opt-out of sharing your personal information with third parties by emailing support@Leafly.com. Please note that deletion of your personal information or content does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information posted on the Services.

When you visit the Site, we and others give you the following choices about use of mechanisms for tracking, including tracking of your online activities over time and across different websites and online services by third parties. Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies from our Site or from third parties. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Site. To opt-out of Google Analytics web tracking for certain browsers, you can download [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).  You may opt out of other cookies that may be present on the Site by following the directions on  [Google’s opt-out page](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin) and  [Quantcast’s opt out page](https://www.quantcast.com/opt-out).  You can also choose to opt-out of use of cookies by some of our third-party advertising partners to deliver ads tailored to your profile and preferences. However, while we and others give you choices as described in this policy, there are many ways in which Web browser signals and other similar mechanisms can indicate your choice to disable tracking, and our Site may not be aware of or honor every mechanism.

You may decline to share certain data with Leafly, in which case we may not be able to provide you with some of the features and functionality of the Site or Service. You may have the right to know what personal information Leafly has about you and to correct any inaccuracies.  Please direct any such requests by email to support@leafly.com or by one of the other means listed below.

Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy

From time to time, we may revise the Policy. To help you stay current of any changes, we note the date the Privacy Policy was last updated above. You agree to review the Policy periodically so that you are aware of any modifications. Continued use of Leafly Site or Services following notice of such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

Dispute Resolution

If you believe that Leafly has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Leafly by e-mail at support@Leafly.com. We will do our best to address your concerns. If you feel that your complaint has been addressed incompletely, we invite you to let us know for further investigation.

Leafly Contact Information

Please contact Leafly with any questions or comments about this Policy, your information, our third-party disclosure practices, or your consent choices.

Leafly Holdings, Inc.

Attention: Privacy Officer

71 Columbia Street, Suite 300

Seattle, WA 98104

Email:  [support@leafly.com](mailto:support@leafly.com)

Leafly Canada Ltd.

Attention: Privacy Officer

Suite 2400, 745 Thurlow Street

Vancouver, BC V6E 0C5

Email:  [support@leafly.com](mailto:support@leafly.com)

Leafly Holdings GmbH

Attention: Privacy Officer

Kemperplatz 1

10785 Berlin

Email: kontakt@leafly.de
